question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                       "question": "Enthalpy is a measure of the energy that is not available for work during a thermodynamic process.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The Doppler effect applies to light.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature", "question": "Sugar contains fat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "&quot;Tachycardia&quot; or &quot;Tachyarrhythmia&quot; refers to a resting heart-rate near or over 100 BPM.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                      "question": "A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Male pandas do handstands while urinating on trees. ", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                       "question": "Polaris is the brightest star in the northern hemisphere night sky.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                      "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
                 ]
